

Zachary Branson

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Phone: (936) 676-5542

Address: 12106 Jamie Dr. Manor Tx, 78653

Email: zac21261@gmail.com **Website:** zacharybranson.com

GitHub: https://github.com/zac1127

PROFILE

I am 25 years old, and currently a Senior Software Developer at Mattersight. I have been married to my wife Danica, and we recently had our first child Emma. I am a hard-working, detailed programmer, looking for new opportunities to use my skills and expand my knowledge as a software engineer.

Making Responsive, and interactive websites has been a passion of mine since a very young age. Every new web application I make, my goal is to make sure it is better than the last. I would love the opportunity to work, learn, and gain more knowledge and experience at your organization.

Thank you for taking the time to consider me for the open position.

EXPERIENCE

Mattersight

Apr 2018 - Present

Senior Software Developer

I currently work on a team with goals to improve and maintain a large-scale web application. I had the opportunity to work on major projects that improved the functionality and performance of the product. I worked as a full stack developer, with responsibilities that scaled from frontend to backend, and database management.

Mattersight

Software Developer

Jun 2017 - Apr 2018

I currently work on a team with goals to improve and maintain a large-scale web application. I had the opportunity to work on major projects that improved the functionality and performance of the product. I worked as a full stack developer, with responsibilities that scaled from frontend to backend, and database management.

Elevation Church

Feb 2017 - Jun 2017

Web Application Developer (contract position)

Built and maintained a social media like mobile application for staff to track fitness, nutrition, and bible studies. Users have the ability post achievements, add profile pictures, and comment on posts. I built using the Laravel PHP framework with a MySQL backend. I used HTML, CSS, and JOuery for the front-end development.



Web Developer

Software Developer

Other

- HTML
- PHP
- Java
- OOP
- Jenkins

- CSS
- Laravel
- **-** (
- Visual Basic Git

- JavaScript
- MySQL
- C++

Postman

- JQuery
- SQL Server

Redis

EDUCATION



- Stephen F. Austin State University, Nacogdoches, Texas
- ABET (Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology)
 Accredited University, http://www.abet.org/
- Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

REFERENCES

Luke Clement

(501) 773-8100

Developer Team Lead at Mattersight

Managed a team of software developers with goals to improve and maintain a large-scale web application. Luke lead the team, and product in many ways including: architecture, deployments, testing, and support.



(936) 414-6534

M&A advisor at Fleet Ridge Pacific

Fleet Ridge Pacific is a company that handles critical issues surrounding mergers and acquisitions in the healthcare industry.